Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Tracy Early papers
Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3790
Early, William Tracy
164 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
The Tracy Early papers contains professional and personal materials pertaining to newspaper and magazine articles written by Early, correspondence, diaries, photographs, school work, books, and sermons.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Unknown.
Biography/Profile
William Tracy Early was born on 1934 February 20 in Snyder, Texas, to Willis Worley Early and Lillian Marian Walton Early. Tracy was the eldest of three children, one of whom died as a child. He was a member of the Royal Ambassadors, a Southern Baptist organization for young boys grades 1-6. Tracy published his first article in 1947 February for the Ambassador Life, the monthly magazine for the Royal Ambassadors. Tracy graduated Snyder High School on 1950 May 26.
Tracy attended Baylor University from 1950-1954 where he earned a Bachelor of Arts. While attending Baylor University, Tracy was a member of Columbus Avenue Baptist Church. In 1954, he attended a summer school session for American Students at the University of Oslo in Norway.
After graduating Baylor University, Tracy attended Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary in Wake Forest, North Carolina. He graduated with a Bachelor’s of Divinity on 1958 January 17. While attending Southeastern, Tracy was ordained as a Baptist minister on 1957 May 15 on the recommendation of the Wake Forest Baptist Church.
Tracy entered the United States Army as a Chaplain with the rank of First Lieutenant. He was appointed Chaplain on 1957 August 14 and served the 59th AAA Battalion at Fort Bliss, Texas for the duration of his commission. Tracy left active duty on 1959 August 16 and resigned his commission on 1960 February 15.
Upon leaving the Army, Tracy attended Union Theological Seminary in New York City where he earned his Doctor of Theology (which was later converted to a Doctor of Philosophy) on 1963 May 21. His dissertation was titled “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson.”
From 1953-1963, Tracy preached and taught at various churches (see Sidebars, page 469 for a complete listing). Most notably Tracy was an interim minister for the youth at Rosemary Baptist Church in Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina in the summer of 1955. From June to mid-August 1961 he served as the interim pastor at Rocky Point Community Church Congregational in Rocky Point, Long Island, New York. Tracy also served as the interim pastor at the First Presbyterian Church in Nyack, New York, from November 1962-January 1963. Tracy began his first and only permanent pastorate on 15 March 1964 at the Urbanna Baptist Church in Urbanna, Virginia. While living in Urbanna, Tracy engaged in various community activities. He was elected Sunday School Superintendent of the Mid-Tidewater Baptist Association and served as the president of the Urbanna Chamber of Commerce. Additionally, Tracy wrote for several newspapers, most notably the Times-Dispatch in Richmond, Virginia. On 1968 August 25 Tracy preached his last sermon and resigned on 1968 August 31 when he moved to New York City to pursue writing.
In New York City, Tracy worked for the World Church Council as an assistant in the information office from 1968 September 24 to 1969 June 30. However, Tracy wanted to become a freelance journalist specializing in religious news. Tracy wrote for many different religious news services, including the National Catholic News Service (NC) which later changed to the Catholic News Service (CNS) until his death in 2005. Tracy also wrote for the Religious News Service, Interpretive Services, United Methodist Communications, North American News Alliance (NANA), and Ecumenical Press Service (EPS) (see Sidebars pages 499-500 for full listing of news services, published works, and years).
Tracy Early died on 2005 December 16 at St. Luke’s Hospital in New York City. He was buried in Snyder, Texas on 2005 December 22.
Scope and Content
The Tracy Early papers are comprised of newspaper and magazine articles, correspondence, diaries, photographs, books, sermons, newspaper clippings, and school work of Tracy Early, who was a Chaplain, pastor, and freelance journalist. A large majority of the collection is articles written by Tracy Early. Included with articles he wrote are research materials, newspaper clippings, notes, and correspondence that pertain to specific articles. Personal materials include correspondence to and from immediate and extended family members and personal diaries from 1948 until his death in 2005. This collection includes materials pertaining to Early’s life at Baylor University, Southeastern Baptist Seminary, and Union Theological seminary including school work and notes from classes. There is also material regarding Early’s time as an Army Chaplain and regarding the various churches where he was the pastor, most significantly the four years Early spent as the pastor of Urbanna Baptist Church in Urbanna, Virginia.
Arrangement
Original order in the Tracy Early papers was by publisher, topic, or person, arranged generally by date (either forward or backward) within the folder. Original order was maintained as much as possible.
Currently, the collection is arranged in ten series: I. Magazine and Newspaper Articles, II. Personal Materials, III. Subjects, IV. General Correspondence, V. School Work, VI. Sermons, VII. Books, VIII. Photographs, IX. Media, and X. Oversize.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3790. Acquired 0-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
Early, Tracy. Sidebars: Reflections by a Missionary Journalist in New York. (San Marcos: Texas, Never Publishing Again, 2006).
Lefevere, Patricia. “Noted religion journalist dies at 71: friends recall Tracy Early's ecumenism, faith and 'good cheer'.” 2006 January 20. Accessed 2012 April 17.
Pattison, Mark. “'Sidebars' of New York: Late CNS correspondent's memoirs published.” Catholic News Service. Accessed 2012 April 17.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Early, William Tracy, 1934-2005.
Subjects (Organizations)
Catholic News Service.; Columbus Avenue Baptist Church (Waco, Tex.); Religious News Service.; Urbanna Baptist Church (Urbanna, Va.)
Subjects
Journalists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Journalists, Religious.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Diaries.; Essays.; Periodicals.; Research notes.; Sermons.
- Magazine and Newspaper Articles, 1947-2005; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Excellent.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains all drafts, notes, research, clippings, and correspondence pertaining to articles that Tracy Early wrote and published. Arranged by publisher/news service that Tracy Early wrote for.
  - Christianity & Crisis: (1 of 6), 1968, 1973-1974, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (2 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (3 of 6), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (4 of 6), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (5 of 6), 1974, 1978-1979, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (6 of 6), 1979, 1981-1984, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (1 of 3), 1981-1983, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (2 of 3), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (3 of 3), 1981-1983, 1985, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (1 of 3), 1986-1987, 1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (2 of 3), 1986, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Christianity & Crisis: (3 of 3), 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1977, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 3), 1978-1979, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 3), 1979, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (1 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (2 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (3 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Christian Science Monitor: (4 of 4), 1982-1985, 1988-1989, 1991, 1993, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 3), 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 3), 1973, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 4), 1974, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 4), 1974-1975, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 4), 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 4), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (4 of 4), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (1 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (2 of 4), 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (3 of 4), 1979-1980, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance: (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Religion and the Presidency, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Christmas Carols, 1974, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Indian Treaties, 1975-1977, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Catholics and Divorce, 1972, 1975, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - United Feature Syndicate: American Debt: (1 of 2), 1965-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - United Feature Syndicate: American Debt: (2 of 2), 1975, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Lexington and Concord, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Immigration, 1970, 1972, 1975-1976, 1979-1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - United Feature Syndicate: 1876 Centennial, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - United Feature Syndicate: George Washington, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Rome and Christianity, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - United Feature Syndicate: American Food Production, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Evangelicals, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Coffee: (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Coffee: (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Tribalism, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Former Presidents, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Law of the Sea: (1 of 2), 1970, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - United Feature Syndicate: Law of the Sea: (2 of 2), 1976-1977, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Correspondence: (1 of 2), 1976-1980, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Correspondence: (2 of 2), 1989-1992, 1994-1995, 1997-2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Magazine and Newspaper Articles: National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1981, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1981, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 2), 1980-1981, 1983, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1982-1983, 1985, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1981-1983, 1985, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1979, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1981, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 6), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 6), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 6), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 6), 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 6), 1982, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (6 of 6), 1984-1985, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 3), 1978, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 5), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 5), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 5), 1978, 1983-1984, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (5 of 5), 1977, 1984, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1981, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), circa 1962-1963, 1975, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1979-1980, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1984, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (1 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (2 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (3 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - National Catholic News Service: General Articles: (4 of 4), 1980, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)